Here it is from the wide angle. Watch Charlie Kirk's right side of his t-shirt. Watch the
Lavalier lapel mic. Do you see it explode? Let's bring it in just a little bit closer.
Watch this. Put it in a freeze frame. That is the explosion from Charlie Kirk's Lavalier
lapel mic. Want to see it again? Bring it in closer. Remember when we told you that
that was absolutely an exit wound? Yeah, it is. Check the trajectory of the round that
was deployed from that Lavalier lapel mic. That went directly from Charlie Kirk's lapel.
That went directly from underneath Charlie Kirk's wide t-shirt up through his neck and
created the exit wound that we told you was an exit wound immediately when we saw that
exit wound. First we had exploding pagers. Now we have exploding mics. Do you remember
the vector analysis from John Bray? That proves that all of the activity came from the mic
that Charlie Kirk was wearing. Remember the palm gun guy in the brown shirt that shadowy
looking guy with the sunglasses? Yeah, he pushes the detonator. Clear his day.
That's the assassin. That's the guy that pushes the detonator, which perfectly aligns
with the explosion that pushes that projectile through Charlie's right side of his neck and
out the left side creating the exit wound. That might just look like the chaos that
you would expect after someone was publicly executed in broad daylight in front of 3,000
people. But in no way did that trigger man, that assassin in the brown shirt with the
sunglasses act alone. We have video now from Destiny that shows the handoff of this remote
detonator.
We had John Cullen on the program last week and he made a great point about ballistic
acoustics being altered to hide the location of the real shooter. Well, the same can be
said to distract from the fact that there was no shooter. Tyler Robinson did not kill Charlie
Kirk. This guy, brown shirt guy, he's the assassin.